<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Javascript on Natan Santolo</title>
    <link>http://www.natansantolo.com/categories/javascript/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Javascript on Natan Santolo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en_US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.natansantolo.com/categories/javascript/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Instagramas</title>
      <link>http://www.natansantolo.com/post/instagramas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.natansantolo.com/post/instagramas/</guid>
      <description>I built this simple component for Marcela&amp;rsquo;s Website, the idea is to show the latest pictures you&amp;rsquo;ve published in your Instagram.
I tried to make it flexible by adding a few configurations, you can choose the type of render, amount of images, also some flags to hide tags and favorites. See all the possible configurations and examples.
   I also made a test page where you can find more example implementations and some notes about styling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Angular Switchery</title>
      <link>http://www.natansantolo.com/post/angular-switchery/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.natansantolo.com/post/angular-switchery/</guid>
      <description>Alexander built this beautiful checkbox component called Switchery. From their website: &amp;laquo;Switchery is a simple component that helps you turn your default HTML checkbox inputs into beautiful iOS 7 style switches in just few simple steps. You can easily customize switches, so that they match your design perfectly.&amp;raquo;
I&amp;rsquo;ve used it along different projects, I&amp;rsquo;m really happy with it. But when I tried to included in a project using AngularJS, I found a few challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Todo App with Chico UI</title>
      <link>http://www.natansantolo.com/post/todo-app-with-chico-ui/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.natansantolo.com/post/todo-app-with-chico-ui/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been following the buzz around Chico UI lately, and I&amp;rsquo;ve found a lot of interesting thoughts, like this guy (don&amp;rsquo;t remember the name) saying that the only thing that is missing, is a Todo App demo builded with Chico. I actually, don&amp;rsquo;t think we need one, but any way, I builded one and I published it there in Github.

Although I&amp;rsquo;m no longer working in the Chico&amp;rsquo;s dev team, I can say that this framework is not aiming to solve architecture or structure issues on web apps, like Backbone (great tool by the way) or Spine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>